<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nutrition on Healthy Bites</title>
    <link>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/tags/nutrition/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nutrition on Healthy Bites</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/tags/nutrition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience It All</title>
      <link>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20161004-experience-it-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20161004-experience-it-all/</guid>
      <description>You need to fix your relationship with food. Food was created to nourish your body and to be enjoyed in the right way. Not to be abused. You need to fix your relationship with food. You cannot use it as a tool to make you feel better when you are down or needs comfort. Balance is the key, whenever you exaggerate anything it becomes unhealthy.
Too much of a good thing isn’t always that great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detox Your Life</title>
      <link>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160926-detox-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160926-detox-your-life/</guid>
      <description>We live in a consumer driven age, in a consumer driven world. Everything needs to be quick and easy, and if it’s not, we are not interested. So we do the same with our health. A 3-day detox, or a 2 week diet. We do not realise how much damage the diet culture is doing to our health.
We came to a point where people are willing to damage their health just to be thin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Peace With Yourself</title>
      <link>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160922-make-peace-with-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160922-make-peace-with-yourself/</guid>
      <description>If I asked you, who you would like to look like, what would you say? You’ll probably say some movie star, model or athlete. If I asked your how happy you are with the way you look, what will your answer be?
I wonder if we were to ask the people whose names and bodies popped into our heads with the first few questions how happy they are with their bodies, what their answers would’ve been?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where it all began – My Story</title>
      <link>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160903-my-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curiousmongoose.github.io/healthybites2018/blog/20160903-my-story/</guid>
      <description>People love to ask me why I became a dietitian. I weren’t always sure why&amp;hellip;
I am not even always sure that I chose it as much as it chose me&amp;hellip;
When I look back it is as if life was always busy preparing me for that day&amp;hellip; I grew up on a farm in the northern regions of South Africa. As a child I had the opportunity to regularly eat fresh home grown food.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>